SBONELO MKHIZE

35 JULES, JEPPESTOWN, JHB 2043

+27 61 069 2364 # SBONELOMKHZE15@MAIL.COM # GITHUB/SBONELO01

Summary

Junior Web Developer with experience in Test Driven Development, API creation, Facilitation and Design Thinking. Supportive and enthusiastic team player with experience working with teams using Git and GitHub. A problem solver and lover of minimalistic design and efficient code.

Skill Highlights

- Agile/Scrum methodology
- TDD

- Optimization
- API development

Work Experience

Junior Web Development Facilitator – 1 June 2020 - present **Umuzi.org**, **Johannesburg**

- Mentor junior developers.
- Host workshops on new topics/technologies for junior developers.
- Review code for web developers before they join product teams.

Junior Web Developer – 02 Sept. 2019 - 01 June 2020 Umuzi.org, Johannesburg

- RESTful API consumption and creation.
- Collaboratively work with a team of web developers and data scientists.
- Work on Python and Node.js projects.

Sales Intern – 12 Nov. 2018 - 12 May 2019

Audi Center Durban, Durban

- Worked with historic data to work out possible resales.
- Effectively used the in-house CRM for finding new deals.
- Collaboratively worked with all departments to gather referral data.

Education

National Certificate in Information Technology (SAQA ID 48872)

System Development Umuzi Academy, JHB

Media and Communication / Political Science

Bachelors Degree - incomplete **University Of Kwa-Zulu Natal, KZN**